Adan Cui

Senior Frontend & Blockchain Engineer

A developer with the best skills and passion in the frontend and blockchain fields. With many years of experience, I have the skills that cannot be ignored in Frontend, Web3, Solidity, Smart Contract, NFT, etc., and an elated developer who can develop further is waiting for you.



- yeshealer@gmail.com
- Miami, Florida, United State
- in linkedin.com/in/yeshealer
- github.com/yeshealer
- medium.com/@yeshealer

- +1 (401) 212-4522
- yeshealer.vercel.app
- S live:.cid.e9fc84427ca181a2
- stackoverflow.com/users/18228536/yeshealer

WORK EXPERIENCE

FullStack Developer 9s Seafood

07/2020 - 11/2020

Remote

9s Seafood provides both fresh & frozen seafood delivery right to your doorstep. Achievements/Tasks

- Updated and completed 9s Seafood site (Frontend * using Codeigniter).
- Add new delivery function for clients (Backend * using PHP).
- Led the a team of 2 student developers.

Senior Frontend & Web3 Developer Croxswap

02/2021 - 07/2021

CroxSwap is a fully decentralized next-generation yield farming protocol which offers dual rewards for staking and farming.

Achievements/Tasks

- Initially completed Croxswap Frontend with 2 members.
- Implemented wallet connect, farming, pooling, dual-farming(only live on Croxswap) using web3.
- Had good understand about connecting between Web3 and solidity.
- Also learned a good knowledge about Smart Contract.

Senior Frontend & Blockchain Developer Formation Finance

09/2021 - 12/2021

The End of Yield Chasing. Welcome to Cross-Chain Risk Parity Smart Farming 2.0. Achievements/Tasks

- Updated Formation Finance frontend to modern.
- Complete the Bridge Smart Contract section.
- Implemented swap, stable swap, pool, dark pool using web3.

EDUCATION

Computer Science **Boston University**

01/2017 - 05/2020

Courses

Web design

 Web development Game development Boston, USA

SKILLS

Smart Contract

HTML

TailwindCSS

COMPLETED PROJECTS

9s Seafood

https://www.9sseafood.com/

Croxswap

https://app.croxswap.com

Formation Finance

https://formation.fi/

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Net Gaming Football New techs